wheresgeorge.com 2018-12-15

# Where's George? - Official Currency Tracking Project - FAQs, Rules/User Guidelines, and Privacy Policy

* * *

**********

Permalink to this page: privacy.php

Here is our abreviated, simple-to-read, Privacy Policy:

 **#1 Personal Information** **  
The staff at _Where's George?_ and _Where's Willy?_ respects your total and complete privacy. We will NEVER sell or distribute your email address or any other personally identifiable information to _anyone, anytime, anywhere._ It will be used solely to notify you of hits on your bills and/or exciting new changes and events at _Where's George?_ and/or _Where's Willy?_.

 **#2 SPAM** **  
If you are receiving and unsolicited email or SPAM, we can assure you that it did not occur as a result of registering at _Where's George?_ or _Where's Willy?_. Nobody other than the staff of the website has access to the user list, and we have not and will not distribute, share, or sell the email/user list to anyone.

 **#3 User Profiles** **  
If you register and set up a Personal User Profile, _Where's George?_ and/or _Where's Willy?_ we will not be responsible for any information you provide in your User Profile, as the User Profiles are open to the public. Please be careful with the email address you place in your User Profile or post on the Public Forums, as web crawlers can capture your information from these pages. Also, the staff of _Where's George?_ and/or _Where's Willy?_ will not be responsible for any information posted in someone else's User Profile. If you find something offensive in a User Profile, you can report it to us using the Contact Us page, and we will investigate it.

 **#4 Registration** **  
Registering at _Where's George?_ also automatically registers you at [_Where's Willy?_](http://www.whereswilly.com/)

 **#5 Cookies** **  
 _Where's George?_ uses a browser cookie to remember who you are, so when you return, you are automatically logged in. We do not collect, sell or distribute any personally identifiable information with the cookie. They are used for your convenience and internal uses only. For more information, please see the Cookie FAQ.

* * *

Here is our full, more complicated, legal mumbo-jumbo, Privacy Policy:  

 **#1 Data** **  
We use technologies like cookies (small files stored by your browser), web beacons, or unique device identifiers to anonymously identify your computer or device so we can deliver a better experience. Our systems also log information like your browser, operating system and IP address.

 **#2 Location** **  
We also may collect personally identifiable information that you provide to us, such as your name or email address. With your permission, we may also access other personal information on your device, such as your phone book, calendar or messages, in order to provide services to you. If authorized by you, we may also access profile and other information from services like Facebook or Twitter.

Our systems are not designed to associate personal information with your activities (such as pages you view or things you click on or search for).

We do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. If you believe we have inadvertently collected such information, please contact us so we can promptly obtain parental consent or remove the information.

 **#3 Location** **  
To customize our service for you, we may collect and store your geographic location as part of your user record. This data is not shared with others.  

 **#4 Access** **  
You can sign into your account to see any personally identifiable information we have stored, such as your name or email address. You can also contact us by email to request to see this information.

 **#5 Deletion** **  
We remove personally identifiable information (such as your name, email address, or location) and other preferences associated with your account promptly after we delete your account. We may retain other non-identifiable data indefinitely.

 **#6 Sharing** **  
We **do not share** personally identifiable information (such as name, email, or location) with other companies.  We may share non-identifiable data to academic or non-profit entities in order to conduct research on human mobility. 

 **#7 Ad Tracking** **  
Ad companies may use and collect anonymous data about your interests to customize content and advertising here and in other sites and applications. Interest and location data may be linked to your device, but is not linked to your identity.

 **#8 Contact** **  
If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies, please contact us:  
Where's George? LLC   
258 Harvard St. #333   
Brookline, MA 02446

 **#9 Vendors** **  
Analytics companies may access anonymous data (such as your IP address or device ID) to help us understand how our services are used. They use this data solely on our behalf. They do not share it except in aggregate form; no data is shared as to any individual user.

 **#10 Security** **  
We take reasonable steps to secure your personally identifiable information against unauthorized access or disclosure. We encrypt transmission of data on pages where you provide payment information. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error.

Information we collect may be stored or processed on computers located in any country where we do business.

 **#11 Special** **  
To operate the service, we also may make identifiable and anonymous information available to third parties in these limited circumstances: (1) with your express consent, (2) when we have a good faith belief it is required by law, (3) when we have a good faith belief it is necessary to protect our rights or property, or (4) to any successor or purchaser in a merger, acquisition, liquidation, dissolution or sale of assets. Your consent will not be required for disclosure in these cases, but we will attempt to notify you, to the extent permitted by law to do so.

 **#12 Summary** **  
This privacy policy was last updated on Wednesday, May 1, 2013. Our privacy policy may change from time to time. If we make any material changes to our policies, we will place a prominent notice on our website or application. If the change materially affects registered users, we will send a notice to you by email.**

**

**

**

**

**

**

**

**

**

**

**

**

**

**

**

**

 ** ** ******************
